Thompson, Mark, Papers /3048
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Mark Thompson Papers
1957-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thompson, Mark
/3048
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Collection consists mostly of Mexican labor publications.
8436110
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4073: James O. Morris Office Files 6007: U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications 6205: NAA Committee Files 6206: Clyde Summers Office Files
Thompson, Mark
8436110
- "Lux" Magazine (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- "Lux" Magazine (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sindicato Mexicano de Electronica (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Sindicato Mexicano de Electronica (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Companeros Electricistas (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Electronica (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Newspapers (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Solidaridad" (1957) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "Solidaridad" (1958) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- "Solidaridad" (1959) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "Solidaridad" (1960) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- "Solidaridad" (1961) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- "Solidaridad" (1962) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- "Solidaridad" (1963) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- "Solidaridad" (1964) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- "Solidaridad" (1965) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- "Solidaridad" (1966) (Box 1, Folder 17)